workplace.com 2013-02-25

# Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment to Privacy

At Workplace Technologies, your privacy is important to us and we are committed to protecting your privacy. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the workplace.com website. On some pages, you can order services, make requests, and submit property address or parcel information. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Company Name, Address, Email address, Phone number, Borrower Name and/or Loan Number.

The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself, your borrower, or your borrower's loan number when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related products or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions with each email. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties without your express written consent.

Finally, at Workplace Technologies, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Third Party Links

This website may contain links to third party websites that are not controlled by Workplace Technologies. These third party links are made available to you as a convenience and you agree to use these links at your own risk. Please be aware that Workplace Technologies is not responsible for the content of third party Websites linked to the Workplace Technologies website, nor are we responsible for the privacy policy or practices of third party websites linked to the Workplace Technologies websites. Our Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect from you while you are at and while you are actively in a session with the Workplace Technologies website. If you should link to a third party Website from the Workplace Technologies website, we strongly encourage you to review and become familiar with that Website's privacy policy. Changes in Our Privacy Policy We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without providing you with advance notice of our intent to make the changes.

How to Contact Us

Please click here to access our Contact Us page.
